Hi. So I'm doing the Soap Opera Digest crossword puzzle..
嗨，我在填《肥皂劇文摘》的 字謎遊戲
and guess who is the clue for three down?
你猜誰是三下的 字謎提示？
"Days of Our Lives star, blank Tribbiani."
「我們的日子的大明星 空三格崔比亞尼」
That's me! I'm blank!
就是我，我是空三格
How cool! We know three down. I'm touching three down.
太酷了，我們認識空三格 我在碰空三格
Yeah, you are, baby.
沒錯，寶貝
Three down knows I'm married. What's three down doing?
空三格知道我結婚了 空三格在做什麼？
Do they call to tell you you're in it?
他們有通知你上了雜誌嗎？
No. They wanted to do a profile on me. I said no.
不，他們想做人物專訪 我拒絕了
Why'd you say no?
為什麼？
Remember the last interview I did?
還記得我上次接受採訪的結果嗎？
I said I write my own lines, the writers got mad..
我說我自己寫台詞 編劇抓狂
and I fell down an elevator shaft. Who knows what I'd say now?
我摔下電梯間 誰知道這次我會說什麼？
If only there was something in your head to control what you say.
你得控制自己說的 每一句話
Come on, you'll keep it in check this time.
少來了 這次你會表現的很好
The publicity would be good for you. You deserve that.
讀者會喜歡你 你有那個實力
In the interview, you could mention, I don't know, "gal pal Rachel Green."
在專訪裡你可以提到 我不知道「女性朋友瑞秋葛林」
Is that "gal pal" spelled L-O-S-E-R?
「女性朋友」的意思是失敗者嗎？
-Okay, don't listen to him. Please? -Fine, all right, I'll do it.
-好吧，別聽他的，拜託 -好吧，我會那麼說的
You have to be there to stop me if I say something stupid.
你們得在場 阻止我說出蠢話
Just then, or all the time? Because we have jobs, you know?
你只指專訪時還是一輩子？ 因為我們還得去上班
We'll be there the whole time. Just remember:
我們會在場的 但你得記住
Gal pal, Rachel Green.
女性朋友瑞秋葛林
I'm gonna be in Soap Opera Digest! And not just in the dumb crossword.
我要上《肥皂劇文摘》了 不只是上愚蠢的字謎遊戲
Seriously, proud of you.
我真的以你為榮
The One With Joey's Interview
本集播出：專訪喬伊
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
-Thanks for taking the time for this. -Not at all. Happy to do it.
-謝謝你抽空接受訪問 -別客氣，我很樂意
You think we're being obvious?
你們覺得我們很明顯嗎？
No. We're just four people with neck problems, who talk like this.
不，我們只是四個脖子有問題 會這樣子說話的人
It's great that we met here.
約在這裡見面是個好主意
When people hear the magazine's paying, they want a big, fancy restaurant.
大家聽說雜誌社會付錢 都會約到高級大餐廳
Actually, I didn't know the magazine was paying.
我真的不知道 雜誌社會付錢
Wouldn't have mattered. I do this for the fans, not the free food.
那不重要 我這麼做是為了影迷，不是為了白吃
-Can I get you anything? -Coffee.
-你們要點些什麼？ -咖啡
And I'll have all the muffins.
各種鬆餅通通來一份
-Hey. -We're not talking.
-嘿 -我們不能說話
Oh, finally.
終於
According to your bio, you've done quite a bit of work.
根據你的個人資料
以前你做過很多工作
Anything that you're particularly proud of?
有哪個工作 是你覺得很驕傲的？
All you want is a dingle
你只要一個小山谷
What you envy's a shwang
你的嫉妒是不需要的
A thing through which you can tinkle
一個可以讓你引以為傲的東西
Or play with, or simply let hang
或是玩弄、掛在身上的東西
This ever happen? You want a glass of milk..
有可能嗎？ 你想喝杯牛奶
but these darn cartons are so hard to open!
但紙盒 很難打開
Boy, you said it, Mike.
天啊，你說的對，麥克
-There 's gotta be a better way! - There is, Kevin!
-一定有更棒的辦法 -沒錯，凱文
This is the first time he's ever used this. It's easy.
這是他第一次使用它 很簡單的
-This works in any milk carton. -It is easy.
-這適用於所有牛奶紙盒 -很簡單
Now I can have milk every day.
現在我每天都能喝牛奶
So this is it, Victor?
就這樣？維多
Yeah, I guess it is. And so..
我猜是吧，所以
I'm gonna get on this spaceship..
我要搭上這艘太空船
and I'm gonna go to Blargon 7 in search of alternative fuels.
到巴拉根七號星 尋找另類能源
But when I return 200 years from now, you'll be long gone.
但兩百年後我再回來 你早已經不在
But I won't have aged at all.
我卻一點都不會變老
So you tell your great-great- granddaughter to look me up.
你得要你的曾曾孫女 來找我
Because, Adrian..
因為，艾德莉恩
baby..
寶貝
I'm gonna want to meet her.
我想見見她
Here I come. I'm coming to fix the copier.
我要出現了 我要來修影印機
I can't get to the copier. I'm thinking, "What do I do?"
我沒辦法靠近影印機 心想「我該怎麼辦？」
So I just watch them have sex. And then I say.. Wait, here's my line:
我看著他們做愛 然後我說…等一下，這是我的台詞
You know, that's bad for the paper tray.
你知道嗎？ 那會把送紙夾弄壞
-Nice work, my friend. -Wait, you see me again.
-做的好，我的朋友 -等一下，我又出現了
Hang on, the guy's butt's blocking me.
等一下，那傢伙的屁股擋到我了
There I am. There I am. There I am.
我出現了，我出現了 我出現了
There are so many things, it's hard to pick just one.
我做過太多工作 要選一個真的很難
I'm getting coffee. Want anything?
我要去拿咖啡，你們需要什麼東西嗎？
-A blueberry muffin and chamomile tea. -Double latte.
-我要藍莓鬆餅跟甘菊茶 -雙份拿鐵
-A bagel with only.. -I was just being polite.
-我要貝果加… -我只是禮貌性問一下
How about when you're not working? What do you do in your spare time?
你不工作的時候呢？ 你有空時都在做什麼？
Look at this clown. He thinks he can take up the whole river.
看看這個小丑 他以為整條河都是他的
Get out of the way, jackass!
別擋路，混蛋
Who names their boat Coast Guard, anyway?
誰會把自己的船 取名為「海岸防衛隊」呢？
That is the Coast Guard.
他們就是海岸防衛隊
What are they doing out here? The coast is way over there!
他們在這裡做什麼？ 海岸在那邊
This is unbelievable.
太不可思議了
Joey has been holding his breath for almost four minutes.
喬伊已經憋氣 快四分鐘了
Dude, are you trying to kill me?
你想害死我嗎？
Well, I see you've had a very productive day.
看來 今天你真的很忙
-Isn't the cowboy hat a little much? -Come on, it's fun!
-這頂牛仔帽太花了吧？ -來吧，真的很好玩
All right.
好吧
Isn't this a woman's hat?
這不是女人的帽子嗎？
Dude, stop talking crazy and make us some tea.
別說傻話了 快去幫我們泡茶
We have to turn off the porn.
我們得把A片關掉
I think you're right.
我想你說的對
-All right, ready? -One.
-好吧，準備好了嗎？ -一
-Two, three. -Three.
-二，三 -三
That's kind of nice.
那真的很棒
-It's kind of a relief. -Yeah.
-我鬆了一口氣 -對
-You wanna see if we still have it? -Yeah.
-你想看我們還能不能看到它嗎？ -好吧
Free porn! We have free porn here!
我們有免費的A片
In my spare time, I read to the blind.
我有空時會唸書給盲人聽
And I'm also a mento for kids.
我還是孩子們的曼陀珠
-A mento? -You know, a mento. A role model.
-曼陀珠？ -曼陀珠，我是他們的榜樣
-A mento? -Right.
-曼陀珠？ -對
-Like the candy? -As a matter of fact, I do.
-吃的曼陀珠？ -事實上沒錯
Our readers always want to know how soap stars stay in such great shape.
讀者想知道 肥皂劇明星是怎麼維持身材的
Do you have a fitness regime?
你有健身妙方嗎？
We stars usually just try to eat right and get lots of exercise.
明星們會正確地飲食 大量運動
You know we've thrown this without dropping it for an hour?
你知道我們已經丟了一小時的球 球都沒掉嗎？
Are you serious?
真的嗎？
I realized it a half-hour ago, but I didn't want to jinx it.
半小時前我發現這件事 但我不想破壞它
-Wow, we are pretty good at this. -Yeah.
-我們真的很厲害 -對
Hey, we totally forgot about lunch.
我們忘了吃午餐
That's the first time I've ever missed a meal.
這是我第一次 忘了吃飯
My pants are a little loose.
我的褲子都鬆了
What's wrong with you?
你怎麼了？
I got this blinding pain in my stomach when I was lifting weights.
我舉啞鈴時 覺得胃好痛
And then I passed out.
後來我昏了過去
I haven't been able to stand up since. But I don't think it's serious.
我沒辦法站起來 但我想應該沒關係
Sounds like a hernia. Go to the doctor.
聽起來像是疝氣 快去看醫生吧
No way!
不行
If I go to the doctor, it's for this thing sticking out of my stomach!
如果我去看醫生 就得把這玩意夾出我的胃
Why'd I have to start working out again?
我為什麼 要恢復健身的習慣呢？
Damn you, fifteens!
該死的15磅啞鈴
-What is it? -A trifle. It has layers.
-它是什麼？ -鬆糕，它有好幾層
A layer of ladyfingers, then a layer of jam.
一層手指餅乾 然後一層果醬
Then custard, which I made from scratch.
然後是甜凍 我用剩下的東西做的
Raspberries, more ladyfingers, beef sauteed with peas and onions.
覆盆子，手指餅乾 加了豆子跟洋蔥的焗牛肉
Then a little bit more custard.
再加一層甜凍
It tastes like feet.
它的味道好像臭腳丫
I like it.
我喜歡
-Are you kidding? -What's not to like? Custard, good.
-你在開玩笑嗎？ -它有什麼不好的？甜凍，好吃
Jam, good. Meat, good!
果醬，好吃，肉，好吃
Well, you don't look good, Joe.
你的臉色不太好，喬伊
Well, the fridge broke, so I had to eat everything.
冰箱壞了 我得把所有東西吃掉
Cold cuts, ice cream, limes.
冷盤，冰淇淋，萊姆
Hey, what was in that brown jar?
那個棕色罐子裡裝了什麼？
-That's still in there? -Not anymore.
-它還在？ -現在不在了
This piece doesn't have floor on it.
這一塊沒有沾到地板
-Stick to your side. -Hey, come on, now.
-別越界 -少來了
All right, what are we having?
好吧，我們要吃什麼？
I don't believe in these crazy diets. Just everything in moderation.
我不相信瘋狂的節食法 只要正常飲食就行了
Your muffins.
你的鬆餅來了
I'll take those to go.
我要外帶
For the kids.
給孩子們吃
I know what I wanted to ask.
我知道我想問什麼
They killed you off years ago. What happened there?
多年前他們安排你死掉 發生了什麼事？
I said some stuff in an interview I shouldn't have said.
我在一次訪問中 說了我不該說的話
-But that is not gonna happen today. -Understood.
-但今天我不會那麼做 -瞭解
-So, what'd you say back then? -I said that I..
-那時你說了什麼？ -我說我…
-Hey, Joey! -How you doing?
-嘿，喬伊 -你好嗎？
This is Shelly. She's interviewing me. Shelly, these are my friends.
她是雪麗，她在訪問我 雪麗，他們是我的朋友
Hi, I'm gal pal Rachel Green. If you want the dirt, come to me.
嗨，我是女性朋友瑞秋葛林 你想知道八卦消息就來找我
This might be Joey's baby, who knows?
這可能是喬伊的孩子，誰知道呢？
I'm just kidding. Seriously, gal pal Rachel Green.
我只是在開玩笑 我只是女性朋友瑞秋葛林
Who just lost the respect of her unborn child.
她剛剛丟夠了 她還沒有出世的孩子的臉
I'm gonna go get this warmed up.
我得去加點熱水
-You're doing great. -So far, nothing stupid.
-你表現的很好 -到目前為止沒有說傻話
-Mento? -No, thanks.
-曼陀珠？ -不，謝謝
As Joey's friends, is there anything our readers should know?
身為喬伊的朋友 有什麼事是讀者應該知道的嗎？
No, just that he is a great guy.
不，他是個大好人
That'll get you into Soap Opera Digest.
你可以上 《肥皂劇文摘》
Well, I..
我…
I'd like to say that Joey..
我想說喬伊
truly has enriched the days of our lives.
真的豐富了 我們的生活
I think that you don't expect someone so hot to be so sweet.
你應該沒想到 這麼性感的男人會那麼體貼
-I like that. What's your name? -Phoebe Buffay.
-我喜歡，你叫什麼名字？ -菲比布非
-How do you spell that? -It's P as in Phoebe. H as in Heebie.
-要怎麼拼？ -菲比的P，希比的H
O as in Obie. E as in Ebie.
歐比的O，艾比的E
B as in Beebee. And E as in, "ello there, mate!"
比比的B E是「哈囉，朋友」
Great. It was nice meeting you.
太棒了，很高興能認識你們
-Yeah, you too. -Thanks.
-對，我也是 -謝謝
It seems you have a lot of friends. Who is your best friend?
你似乎有很多朋友 誰是你最好的朋友？
How come you have two?
你為什麼會有兩個？
Well, this one's for you.
這個是送你的
-Get out! -No, I can't.
-不可能 -對，不可能
I know how much this means to you. This isn't just about jewelry.
我知道這對你來說意義重大 這不只是首飾而已
It's about you and me and the fact that we're best buds.
它代表了 你跟我是最好的朋友
Is this friendship? I think so!
這是友誼嗎？我想是的
Check it out! We're bracelet buddies!
你看，我們是手鐲兄弟
That's what they'll call us!
他們是那樣子叫我們的
-I'm sorry. -It's all right. Don't worry about it.
-對不起 -沒關係，別擔心
That's gonna leave a stain.
它會留下印子
Rach, hey, it's fine. You're at Joey's.
瑞秋，沒關係 你在喬伊家
-Really? -Yeah, look.
-真的嗎？ -對，你看
-I've never lived like this before. -I know!
-我沒有過過這種生活 -我知道
Well, don't waste it. I mean, it's still food. Jeez!
別浪費它 它還是食物，天啊
I feel guilty. I wanna be a good friend..
我覺得有罪惡感 我想當個好朋友
and damn it, I am a good friend. So shut up and close your eyes.
該死，我是個好朋友 閉上你的嘴巴跟眼睛
You are a good friend.
你是個好朋友
The audition was this morning, and I didn't get it.
我今天早上去試鏡 但我失敗了
But that was a hell of a kiss. Rachel is a very lucky girl.
那個吻真的很棒 瑞秋是個幸運的女孩
Let's get the contestants out of their isolation booths.
請參賽者離開 隔離區
And they're off!
他們出發了
Get your foot off my contestant! Judge!
別擋住我的選手 裁判
Judge rules: No violation.
裁判判決沒有犯規
-The duck gets the Nutter Butter! -No! That's just an old won ton.
-鴨子踩到奶油了 -不，那是以前掉的餛飩
Judge rules: Nutter Butter!
裁判判決是奶油
Tough call.
真的很難決定
-I saw it on the Discovery Channel. -Wait a minute. I saw that!
-我在探索頻道看過 -等一下，我看過它
Yeah, about jellyfish, and how if you..
對，關於水母 如果你…
You peed on yourself?
你尿在自己身上？
You can't say that! You don't know!
別那麼說，你不瞭解那有多痛
I thought I'd pass out from the pain.
我以為我會痛得昏過去
Anyway, I tried, but I couldn't bend that way.
總之我試過了 但我沒辦法那樣子彎曲身子
So..
所以
That's right, I stepped up!
沒錯，我幫了她一個大忙
She's my friend and she needed help!
她是我的朋友，她需要幫忙
If I had to, I'd pee on any one of you!
有必要的話 我會尿在你們身上
Nope. No best friend.
不，我沒有最好的朋友
Just a lot of close friends.
我只有很多密友
So now back to the show.
現在言歸正傳
How does it feel to have a huge gay fan base?
有那麼多男同志支持你 你有什麼感覺？
Really? Me?
真的嗎？我？
Wow, I don't even know any huge gay people.
我不認識 任何男同志
It hurts me. It physically hurts me.
我真的覺得心好痛
Now, off the record, you're not..
這是我們的私下談話，你不是
What? Are you referring to my man's bag?
什麼？ 你在質疑我的男子氣概嗎？
At first, it just looked good, but it's practical.
剛開始它只是看起來不錯 但它真的很實用
It's got compartments for stuff: your wallet, your keys.
它有很多放東西的小袋子 你可以放皮夾，鑰匙
Your makeup.
化妝品
Should I climb down your front so we're face to face..
我要從你的正面滑下 讓我們面對面
or should I climb down your back so we're butt to face?
還是從你的背面滑下 屁股對臉？
-I think face is best. -Yeah, face.
-我想面對面比較好 -對，面對面
-Okay, here I come. -All right.
-好吧，我來了 -好吧
Oh, my.. How much do you weigh, Ross?
天啊… 你有多重？羅斯
I prefer not to answer that. I'm still carrying a little holiday weight.
我不想回答那個問題 假日結束後我胖了不少
When we said "face to face, " we didn't think it all the way through!
我們說「面對面」時 我們沒有想清楚
-Hey, Pheebs. -Hey.
-嘿，菲比 -嘿
Check it out.
你看
How much of a man am I?
我很有男子氣概吧？
Nice. Manly and also kind of a slut.
太棒了，你是男子漢也是個蕩婦
You're turning into a woman.
你變成女人了
No, I'm not! Why would you say that? That's just mean!
不，你為什麼會那麼說？ 那太傷人了
Now I've upset you? What did I say?
我惹毛你了？ 我說了什麼？
Not what you said, it's just the way you said it.
不是你說的話 是你的語氣
Oh, my God! I'm a woman!
天啊，我是個女人
-Great nap. -It really was.
-我睡得很熟 -沒錯
Me? Gay? No. No. No.
我？男同志？不
But I have a number of close friends who are.
但我有很多密友 是男同志
So let's talk about women.
我們來談談女人
I'm sure our female readers are interested in your romantic life.
我相信女性讀者 對你的愛情生活很有興趣
What I do is, I look a woman up and down and I say:
我會看著女人 跟她說
"Hey. How you doing?"
「嘿，你好嗎？」
Oh, please.
拜託
Hey. How you doing?
嘿，你好嗎？
He has an amazing Porsche under there.
他有一輛很棒的保時捷
I'd love to show you, but I just tucked her in. She's sleeping.
我很樂意讓你們參觀 但我才剛把它停好，它在休息
Would you two girls like to go for a drink?
你們兩個 想去喝一杯嗎？
-Is Rachel here? I'm her sister. -Oh, my God! Jill!
-瑞秋在嗎？我是她妹妹 -天啊，吉兒
-Oh, my God! Rachel! -Oh, hi!
-天啊，瑞秋 -嗨
-Oh, my God! Introduce us! -Well, this is Chandler.
-天啊，快幫我們介紹 -他是錢德
You know Monica and Ross. That's Phoebe. That's Joey.
你認識摩妮卡跟羅斯 她是菲比，他是喬伊
-Hey, how you doing? -Don't!
-嘿，你好嗎？ -不要
You're a really nice guy. I'm happy to be your roommate and friend.
你是個好人 我喜歡當你的室友跟朋友
I'm just.. You know, I just don't feel that way about you.
我只是你知道的 我對你沒有那種感覺
I see what happened.
我知道發生了什麼事
It's because I was trying to repel you. Right?
那是因為 我試著抗拒你，對吧？
Believe me, you'd feel a lot different if I turned it on.
相信我 我發動攻勢後，你會有不同的感覺
-I don't think so. -Oh, I do.
-我不那麼認為 -我那麼認為
How you doing?
你好嗎？
I'm okay.
我很好
What? Oh, dear God!
什麼？天啊
Not much to tell there. I'm really shy.
沒什麼好說的 我真的很害羞
So that's it. I guess that's all I need.
好了 我猜我已經問完了
Thank you so much. I think they'll run this next month.
謝謝你 我想應該下一期就會刊出
Oh, great. Great. Thank you.
太棒了，謝謝你
-Bye. -Bye-bye.
-再見 -拜拜
-I did it. -Amazing.
-我辦到了 -太棒了
Wait, I almost forgot. We have to ask everybody this:
等一下，我差點忘了 我們得問每個人這個問題
Other than Days, what's your favorite soap opera?
除了「我們的日子」以外 你最喜歡哪出肥皂劇？
Oh, I don't watch soap operas. Excuse me? I have a life, you know?
我不看肥皂劇 抱歉，我的生活沒那麼無聊
The readers at Soap Opera Digest will be happy to learn that.
《肥皂劇文摘》的讀者 知道那一點一定會很高興
Good enough.
非常好
So close.
只差一點而已
They didn't put in the part about you not watching soaps.
他們沒登出 你說你不看肥皂劇那一段
I called the lady and said l was joking. She was nice about it.
我打電話告訴那個女記者 我是在開玩笑，她接受了
-You slept with her, didn't you? -A little bit.
-你跟她上床了，對吧？ -可以那麼說
This picture of you is steamy.
你的這張照片有點模糊
That's just a little something for my huge gay fan base.
那是為了配合 我的男同志影迷的喜好
-Did you just wink at me? -You're the one who loves the picture.
-你在跟我眨眼睛嗎？ -你喜歡那張照片